No one ever thinks it'll happen
until it does.
(Leonard:)Penny, if you promise not to chew the flesh
off our bones while we sleep, you can stay.
- Ha. What?
- He's engaging in reductio ad absurdum.
It's the fallacy of extending someone's
argument to ridiculous proportions...
...and then criticizing the result.
And I don't appreciate it.
(Leonard:)I'll get you a blanket and a pillow.
Okay, since I'm obviously being ignored
here, let's go over the morning schedule.
I use the bathroom from 7 to 7:20.
Plan your ablutions
and bodily functions accordingly.
(Penny:)How am I supposed to
plan my bodily functions?
(Sheldon:)I suggest no liquids after 11p.m.
- Here you go.
- Thanks, Leonard.
Heh, wrong.
(Penny:)I'm listening.
(Sheldon:)Your head goes on the other end.
- Why?
- It's culturally universal.
(Sheldon:)A bed, even a temporary bed...
(Sheldon:)...is always oriented with the headboard
away from the door.